The motto of this year’s BMW Group
Report is “Already ahead”.
It is indeed a confident statement.
And we back it up
– as always – with facts.
This bold claim applies to our stable
and profitable business model –
even and especially in a highly volatile
environment.
It also applies to BMW’s
consistent and long-term
strategic orientation.
For our customers worldwide,
we bring innovation to life
in our vehicles –
offering them unparalleled sheer
driving pleasure.
The new BMW iX3 is the first vehicle
of our NEUE KLASSE.
Demand is high
and even exceeds our expectations.
And the iX3 is just the beginning.
We are now rolling out the NEUE
KLASSE technologies across the entire
BMW portfolio: in the 3 Series,
the 7 Series,
and the X5 – to name
just a few of the new models
launching this year.
Take a look at our online report
to see for yourself
how well the company is performing.
There are also four exciting stories
from across the BMW Group to explore.
“Already ahead” is not only our claim,
but a reality we live by.